Simon Fraser University Gallery fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Exhibition files, 1968-2001, predominant 1968-1987; F-90-5; 2.43 m of textual records
  - Individual exhibition files, 1968-2001, predominant 1968-1987; F-90-5-2; 2.37 m of textual records and other material; Dates: the exhibition case files (one file for each exhibition) run to 1987; after this year, there are only 2 additional files (266 and 267) containing material relating to exh
    - Grupo Piru, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-164 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 4-22, 1980.
      Grupo Piru; Textual records
    - Sekino Jun'ichiro - woodcuts, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-165 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 5-30, 1980.
      Sekino Jun'ichiro; Textual records
    - Ronald Sandor - photomurals and sculpture, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-166 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 8 - May 2, 1980. Includes 20 photos and 30 negatives.
      Ronald Sandor; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - John Charnetski: sculpture, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-167 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between May 18 - Aug. 8, 1980. Includes 17 photos and 1 contact sheet.
      John A. Charnetski; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Amish quilts, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-168 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between May 12 - June 13, 1980.
    - National print show 1979, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-169 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between June 23 - July 11, 1980.
    - T-shirt day 1980, F-90-5-2-0-170 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between July 13, 1980.
    - Aspects of Canadian printmaking, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-171 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between July 12 - Aug. 15, 1980.
    - The Huichol of Mexico, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-172 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 8 - Oct. 3, 1980.
    - Gregorio Sulca - weaving, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-173 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 24-26, 1980.
      Gregorio Sulca; Textual records
    - On canvas 1980, F-90-5-2-0-174 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 13 - Oct. 10, 1980. Includes 37 slides.
    - On canvas 1980 - planning and production, F-90-5-2-0-175 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Includes 22 negatives, 2 photos, 1 contact sheet.
    - Canadians / Canadiens, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-176 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 10 - Nov. 2, 1980.
    - First exhibition, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-177 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 10 - Dec. 5, 1980.
    - Musical manuscripts, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-178 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 5-30, 1981. Includes 58 slides, 1 photograph.
    - Canaletto etchings, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-179 (Archival box - standard 90-19)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 9-27, 1981.
    - Recent acquisitions, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-180 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 9-27, 1981.
    - Rites of passage, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-181 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 23 - May 3, 1981.
    - Emma Lake '79, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-182 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between May 11 - June 5, 1981. Includes 2 photographs.
    - Shipibo painting, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-183 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between June 15 - July 17, 1981.
    - Insights, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-184 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between July 20 - Aug. 14, 1981. Includes 6 photographs.
    - Two views of China, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-185 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 7-25, 1981.
      John Leung; Lam, David; Textual records
    - Robert Young: prints / gravures, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-186 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 5-23, 1981.
      Robert Young; Textual records
    - Dream of Belinda, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-187 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 24, 1981. Includes 1 photograph.
      Henry Fuseli; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Woven images: Bolivian weaving, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-188 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 2-20, 1981. Includes 1 photograph.
    - Swedish graphics, 1981; F-90-5-2-0-189 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 20 - Dec. 18, 1981.
    - Native images from the Simon Fraser collection, 1981 - 1982; F-90-5-2-0-190 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Fall 1981, Spring 1982.
    - Library foyer exhibitions, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-191 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
    - 2nd Biennale of prints and drawings, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-192 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 11 - Feb. 5, 1982.
    - Recent projects - student show, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-193 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 8-26, 1982.
    - Graphic Newfoundland, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-194 (Archival box - standard 90-20)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 5-23, 1982.
    - Graphic Newfoundland - catalogue, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-195 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
    - Graphic Newfoundland - budget, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-196 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
    - Selections - SFU collection, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-197 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 15 - Mar. 5, 1982.
    - Rene Magritte, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-198 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between May 17 - June 11, 1982.
      Rene Magritte; Textual records
    - Special video presentation, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-199 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between June 10-11, 1982.
    - Nanga - Japanese painting, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-200 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between June 14 - July 9, 1982. Includes 4 photographs.
    - The world of Donald Evans, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-201 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between July 19 - Aug. 13, 1982. Includes 2 photographs and 5 slides.
      Evans, Donald; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - The world of Donald Evans, vol. 2, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-202 (Archival box - standard 90-21)
      Exhibition took place between July 19 - Aug. 13, 1982. Includes 2 photographs.
    - The world of Donald Evans, vol. 3, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-203 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between July 19 - Aug. 13, 1982.
      Evans, Donald; Textual records
    - Gordon Smith: prints 1954-1980, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-204 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 7-24, 1982. Includes 2 photographs.
      Smith, Gordon A.; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Tapa and Pandanus, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-205 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 29, 1982.
    - La Serienoire (Ulrich and Daouset), 1982; F-90-5-2-0-206 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 4-22, 1982. Includes 2 phtographs.
      Daouset, Carl; Normand Ulrich; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Andy Sinats: photo screenprints, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-207 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 1-19, 1982. Includes 1 negative and 1 photograph.
      Sinats, Andy; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Solidarity with Solidarnosc, 1982; F-90-5-2-0-208 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 29 - Dec. 17, 1982. Includes 9 photographs and 1 negative.
      Solidarnosc; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Ingeborg Mohr, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-209 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 10-28, 1983. Includes 3 photographs and 2 negatives.
      Ingeborg Mohr; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Haxton: films and photographs, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-210 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 7-25, 1983.
      David Haxton; Textual records
    - Grafica Italiana contemporanea, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-211 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 12-24, 1983.
    - Submissions - student exhibit, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-212 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 7-25, 1983.
    - Maxwell Bates - landscapes, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-213 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 1 - May 6, 1983.
      Maxwell Bates; Textual records
    - Ulayu, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-214 (Archival box - standard 90-22)
      Exhibition took place between May 16 - June 10, 1983. Includes 6 photographs.
      Ulayu; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Recent acquisitions, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-215 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between June 13-30, 1983. Includes 1 photograph and 1 negative.
    - Robert Bowers, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-216 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between July 11 - Aug. 5, 1983. Includes 12 negatives, 1 contact sheet, and 3 photographic prints.
      Robert Bowers; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Soho duo - Higgins and Cleveland, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-217 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 6-23, 1983.
      E.F. Higgins III; Cleveland, Buster; Textual records
    - Visual Arts faculty, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-218 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 3-21, 1983.
      MacWilliam, David; Greg Snider; Jeff Wall; Textual records
    - Visual Arts extravaganza, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-219 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 3, 1983.
    - Private works, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-220 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 31 - Nov. 18, 1983.
    - Malaspina printmakers annual, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-221 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 28 - Dec. 16, 1983.
    - Library foyer exhibits, 1983; F-90-5-2-0-222 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
    - Contemporary Australian printmakers, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-223 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 9-27, 1984. Includes 1 negative and 4 photographs.
    - Architectural designs, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-224 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 31 - Feb. 1, 1984.
    - The prints of Alex Colville, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-225 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 6-24, 1984.
      Colville, Alex; Textual records
    - Visual Arts student annual, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-226 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 5-23, 1984. Includes 19 photographs.
    - Design art by Sobrio (Library), 1984; F-90-5-2-0-227 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 26 - Apr. 9, 1984.
      Florence Sobrio; Textual records
    - Contemporary art of China, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-228 (Archival box - standard 90-23)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 2-20, 1984.
    - Contemporary Polish cultural posters, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-229 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between May 7-25, 1984.
    - Maureen Enns, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-230 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between June 4-22, 1984. Includes 2 photographs.
      Maureen Enns; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Visiting artists, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-231 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between July 3-20, 1984.
      Marian Penner Bancroft; Czartoryski, Chris; Textual records
    - Drawings - Simon Fraser collection, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-232 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between July 30 - Aug. 17, 1984.
    - Water and colour and paper, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-233 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 4-21, 1984. Includes 2 photographs.
    - James Klyman-Mowczan new abstraction, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-234 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 22 - Nov. 16, 1984.
      James Klyman-Mowczan; Textual records
    - The widening sphere, 1984; F-90-5-2-0-235 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 26 - Dec. 14, 1984.
      National Archives of Canada; Textual records
    - Etidlooie Etidlooie, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-236 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 7 - Feb. 1, 1985.
      Etidlooie; Textual records
    - Lyse Lemieux, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-237 (Archival box - standard 90-24)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 11 - Mar. 1, 1985.
      Lyse Lemieux; Textual records
    - New evidence: student show, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-238 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 11-29, 1985.
    - Peace earth peace, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-239 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 8 - May 2, 1985. Includes 1 photograph.
    - The legacy of India - "Life and Work of Nehru", 1985; F-90-5-2-0-240 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between May 13-31, 1985.
      Jawaharlal Nehru; Textual records
    - Inuit etchings and engravings, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-241 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between June 10 - Aug. 9, 1985.
    - SFU cartoon exhibition, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-242 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 9 - Oct. 4, 1985.
    - Chinese peasant painting, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-243 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 14 - Nov. 1, 1985.
    - West coast surrealist group, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-244 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 12 - Dec. 13, 1985. Includes 3 photographs.
      Melmoth Vancouver Group; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Dundarave printmakers, 1985; F-90-5-2-0-245 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 13-31, 1986. Includes 14 photographs, 11 negatives, and 1 contact sheet.
    - Precarious balance series - Barbara Z. Sungur, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-246 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 10-28, 1986.
      Sungur, Barbara Z.; Textual records
    - Visual Arts student show, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-247 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 10-27, 1986.
    - Myfanwy Spencer Pavelic exhibition, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-248 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between May 9-30, 1986.
      Pavelic, Myfanwy Spencer; Textual records
    - Vancouver young artists, vol. 1, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-249 (Archival box - standard 90-25)
      Exhibition took place between June 9-27, 1986. Includes 1 photograph.
    - Vancouver young artists, vol. 2, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-250 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between June 9-27, 1986. Includes 1 photograph and 8 slides.
    - Shan Baiqin exhibit, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-251 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between July 5-25, 1986. Includes 3 photographs.
      Shan Baiqin; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Northwest printmakers, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-252 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Aug. 5-29, 1986. Includes 20 slides.
    - Suskaman-Indonesian puppet, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-253 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 2-12, 1986.
      Sukasman; Textual records
    - Icons of postmodernism, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-254 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 22 - Oct. 2, 1986.
    - New York prints, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-255 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 14 - Nov. 7, 1986.
    - Faculty and staff show, 1986; F-90-5-2-0-256 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 17-Dec.12, 1986.
    - SFU Chinese Student Society show - "Images of China", 1987; F-90-5-2-0-257 (Archival box - standard 90-26)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 26 - Feb. 13, 1987.
    - Hele Kowallek, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-258 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 5-23, 1987.
      Hele Kowallek; Textual records
    - The Bible and the image (exhibition cancelled), 1987; F-90-5-2-0-259 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 2-6, 1987.
      Yeshiahu Nir; Textual records
    - Visual Arts student show, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-260 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 9 - Apr. 3, 1987.
    - Recent acquisitions, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-261 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
    - Faculty and staff photography show, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-262 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between May 14-15, 1987. Includes 1 photograph.
    - Contemporary Canadian drawings, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-263 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between May 20 - June 10, 1987. Includes 1 photograph.
    - Al Razutis, 1987; F-90-5-2-0-264 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Exhibition took place between June 22 - July 10, 1987. Includes 8 photographs.
      Razutis, Al; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - People exhibition, 1983 - 1985; F-90-5-2-0-265 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
      Patrick Sullivan; Textual records
    - Exhibitions - invitations, news releases, posters, 1987 - 1991; F-90-5-2-0-266 (Archival box - standard 90-27)
    - Exhibitions - posters (oversize), 1971 - 2001; F-90-5-2-0-267